[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The panda has an enlarged wristbone that works as an opposable thumb.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Larroquette ha  appeared in both The Practice and Boston Legal as lawyer Carl Sack.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Black Sea reaches the maximum depth of 2,210 m. Its neighbor, the Sea of Azov, is unique in terms of sea depth for what reason?", "correct_answer": "It is the shallowest sea in the world.", "incorrect_answers": ["Its floor sinks constantly because it is located on a large basalt plate.", "It has almost perfectly flat sea floor with a depth of 1370 m.", "It has no established sea floor, it changes constantly with currents."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The earliest known European example of Homo sapiens was discovered in 1868 and was given what name?", "correct_answer": "Cro Magnon Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Neaanderthal Man", "Austrlopithecus", "Peking Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Damon Wayans was not in the 1987 movie Hollywood Shuffle.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What brand of running shoes did fictional character Forrest Gump like to wear?", "correct_answer": "Nike", "incorrect_answers": ["Puma", "Reebok", "Saucony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although too smelly, this member of the onion family is considered to be an aphrodisiac. It also has antioxidant properties and is used in alternative medicine.", "correct_answer": "Garlic", "incorrect_answers": ["Spinach", "Leeks", "Celery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Espresso refers to which of these facts?", "correct_answer": "It could be any or all of these.", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot water is pressed through finely ground coffee.", "The coffee is brewed quickly.", "The coffee should be served and drunk quickly."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that goldfish only have a 3-second memory?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nonmember Runescape players can go to Taverly and kill a couple of druids. Then they can go to Camelot bank and take out 1,000 gold pennies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the short story on which the movie Memento is based?", "correct_answer": "Memento Mori", "incorrect_answers": ["Learn to Forget", "Lost Memories", "Remember Death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy hit Wedding Crashers, Jeremy was taught how to crash weddings by this friend who passed the wedding crashing torch to Jeremy in 1993.", "correct_answer": "Chazz Reinhold", "incorrect_answers": ["Chazz  Palminteri", "Judge Reinhold", "John Gibson"]}]